http://www.drugratingz.com/privacy.jsp

Information Collection and Use
DrugRatingz.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a DrugRatingz.com account, when you visit DrugRatingz.com pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes.
When you register with DrugRatingz.com, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, and zip code. Once you register with DrugRatingz.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
DrugRatingz.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, DrugRatingz.com cookie information and the page you requested.
DrugRatingz.com uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
DrugRatingz.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
DrugRatingz.com may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
We have your consent to share the information;
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of DrugRatingz.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.
Cookies
DrugRatingz.com may set and access DrugRatingz.com cookies on your computer.
DrugRatingz.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to DrugRatingz.com's cookies.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
DrugRatingz.com gives you the ability to edit your DrugRatingz.com Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want DrugRatingz.com to contact you about specials and new products.
Security
Your DrugRatingz.com Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
DrugRatingz.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
The Ratingz Network - Local Ratings and Reviews
Copyright © , Ratingz Inc.  •  Privacy  •  Contact Ratingz  •  Web Design by LunaGraphica
